Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 3. Personal, Political and Official Files, 1944-2010 TJU.2010.01.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Political Party Involvement, 1978-2006; IV.
  - Vote for Homes questionnaire, 2004 (Box 521, Folder 45)
  - Voting analysis, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, 1982 (Box 522, Folder 1)
  - Voting analysis, American Association of Entrepreneurs, 1998 (Box 522, Folder 2)
  - Voting analysis, American Association of University Women, 1984-2001 (Box 522, Folder 3)
  - Voting analysis, American Bakers Association, 1980-1984 (Box 522, Folder 4)
  - Voting analysis, American Cancer Society, 1997-1998 (Box 522, Folder 5)
  - Voting analysis, American Civil Liberties Union, 2002 (Box 522, Folder 6)
  - Voting analysis, American Conservative Union, 1981-1996 (Box 522, Folder 7)
  - Voting analysis, American Farm Bureau Federation, 1984-1996 (Box 522, Folder 8)
  - Voting analysis, American Federation of Government Employees, 1981-1984 (Box 522, Folder 9)
  - Voting analysis, AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education, 1962-1985 (Box 522, Folder 10)
  - Voting analysis, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1981-1996 (Box 522, Folder 11)
  - Voting analysis, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1984 (Box 522, Folder 12)
  - Voting analysis, American Federation of Teachers, 1981-1984 (Box 522, Folder 13)
  - Voting analysis, American Federation of Teachers, 1982-1996 (Box 522, Folder 14)
  - Voting analysis, American Hellenic Educational Progressive Association, 2000 (Box 522, Folder 15)
  - Voting analysis, American Institute of Architects, 1983-1984 (Box 522, Folder 16)
  - Voting analysis, American Parents Committee, 1985 (Box 522, Folder 17)
  - Voting analysis, American Postal Workers Union, 1981-1985 (Box 522, Folder 18)
  - Voting analysis, American Postal Workers Union, 2002 (Box 522, Folder 19)
  - Voting analysis, American Security Council, 1982-1984 (Box 522, Folder 20)
  - Voting analysis, Americans for Democratic Action, 1981-1986 (Box 522, Folder 21)
  - Voting analysis, Americans for Democratic Action, 1981-1996 (Box 522, Folder 22-23)
  - Voting analysis, Americans for Immigration Control, 1994 (Box 522, Folder 24)
  - Voting analysis, Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance, 2002 (Box 522, Folder 25)
  - Voting analysis, Business and Professional Women, 1992-1997 (Box 522, Folder 26)
  - Voting analysis, Communications Workers of America, 1981-1991 (Box 522, Folder 27)
  - Voting analysis, Communications Workers of America, 1981-1996 (Box 522, Folder 28)
  - Voting analysis, Competitive Enterprise Institute, 1985-1996 (Box 522, Folder 29)
  - Voting analysis, Competitive Enterprise Institute, 1990-1992 (Box 522, Folder 30)
  - Voting analysis, Concord Coalition, 2000 (Box 522, Folder 31)
  - Voting analysis, Congressional Black Caucus, 1990-1995 (Box 522, Folder 32)
  - Voting analysis, Congressional Research Service, 1991 (Box 522, Folder 33)
  - Voting analysis, Conservatives against Liberal Legislation, 1982-1985 (Box 522, Folder 34)
  - Voting analysis, Council for a Livable World Education Fund, 1982-1991 (Box 522, Folder 35)
  - Voting analysis, External organizations, 1981-1985 (Box 522, Folder 36)
  - Voting analysis, Friends Committee on National Legislation, 1981-1990 (Box 522, Folder 37)
  - Voting analysis, Fund for Assuring an Independent Retirement, 1983-1989 (Box 522, Folder 38)
  - Voting analysis, Independent Petroleum Association of America, 1982-1991 (Box 523, Folder 1)
  - Voting analysis, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1982-1992 (Box 523, Folder 2)
  - Voting analysis, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1988-1989 (Box 523, Folder 3)
  - Voting analysis, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1983-1991 (Box 523, Folder 4)
  - Voting analysis, John Birch Society, 1982-1991 (Box 523, Folder 5)
  - Voting analysis, JustLife, 1988 (Box 523, Folder 6)
  - Voting analysis, Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1978-1990 (Box 523, Folder 7)
  - Voting analysis, League of Conservation Voters, 1981-1990 (Box 523, Folder 8-9)
  - Voting analysis, League of Women Voters, 1982-1983 (Box 523, Folder 10)
  - Voting analysis, Liberty Lobby, 1984-1989 (Box 523, Folder 11)
  - Voting analysis, March for Life, 1985-1990 (Box 523, Folder 12)
  - Voting analysis, Moral Majority, 1985-1987 (Box 523, Folder 13)
  - Voting analysis, NARAL, 1981-1991 (Box 523, Folder 14)
  - Voting analysis, National Alliance for Senior Citizens, 1981-1983 (Box 523, Folder 15)
  - Voting analysis, NAACP, 1981-1990 (Box 523, Folder 16)
  - Voting analysis, National Association of Letter Carriers, 1984-1991 (Box 523, Folder 17)
  - Voting analysis, National Association of Manufacturers, 1982-1992 (Box 523, Folder 18)
  - Voting analysis, National Association of Realtors, 1984-1988 (Box 523, Folder 19)
  - Voting analysis, National Association of Retired Federal Employees, 1986-1992 (Box 523, Folder 20)
  - Voting analysis, National Association of Retired Federal Employees, 1992-2000 (Box 523, Folder 21)
  - Voting analysis, National Association of Social Workers, 1980-1992 (Box 523, Folder 22)
  - Voting analysis, National Committee for a Human Life Amendment, 1979-1991 (Box 523, Folder 23)
  - Voting analysis, National Committee to Preserve Social Security and Medicare, 1984-1989 (Box 523, Folder 24)
  - Voting analysis, National Committee to Preserve Social Security and Medicare, 1990-1994 (Box 523, Folder 25)
  - Voting analysis, National Council of Senior Citizens, 1983-1991 (Box 523, Folder 26)
  - Voting analysis, National Education Association, 1980-1998 (Box 523, Folder 27)
  - Voting analysis, National Education Association, 1984-1991 (Box 523, Folder 28)
  - Voting analysis, National Farmers Organization, 1981-1990 (Box 523, Folder 29)
  - Voting analysis, National Farmers Organization, 1992 (Box 523, Folder 30)
  - Voting analysis, National Farmers Union, 1991-1996 (Box 523, Folder 31)
  - Voting analysis, National Federation of Federal Employees, 1992 (Box 523, Folder 32)
  - Voting analysis, National Federation of Independent Businesses, 1983-1996 (Box 523, Folder 33)
  - Voting analysis, National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1992 (Box 523, Folder 34)
  - Voting analysis, National Hispanic Leadership Agenda, 2002 (Box 523, Folder 35)
  - Voting analysis, National Hispanic Leadership Agenda, 2003 (Box 523, Folder 36)
  - Voting analysis, National Impact, 1984-1990 (Box 523, Folder 37)
  - Voting analysis, National Journal, 1994 (Box 523, Folder 38)
  - Voting analysis, National League of Cities, 1982-1996 (Box 523, Folder 39)
  - Voting analysis, National Retail Federation, 2001 (Box 523, Folder 40)
  - Voting analysis, National Right to Life Committee, 1982-1996 (Box 523, Folder 41)
  - Voting analysis, National Tax Limitation Committee, 1991 (Box 524, Folder 1)
  - Voting analysis, National Taxpayers Union, 1981-1996 (Box 524, Folder 2)
  - Voting analysis, National Taxpayers Union, 1997-2005 (Box 524, Folder 3)
  - Voting analysis, National Treasury Employees Union, 1990-1993 (Box 524, Folder 4)
  - Voting analysis, National Wildlife Federation, 1994 (Box 524, Folder 5)
  - Voting analysis, National Women's Political Caucus, 1990 (Box 524, Folder 6)
  - Voting analysis, National Write Your Congressman, 1992-1993 (Box 524, Folder 7)
  - Voting analysis, Network, 1992-1996 (Box 524, Folder 8)
  - Voting record, Alliance for Retired Americans, 2003-2004 (Box 524, Folder 9)
  - Voting record, American Federation of Government Employees, 1998-2001 (Box 524, Folder 10)
  - Voting record, American Public Health Association, 2002 (Box 524, Folder 11)
  - Voting record, American Security Council, 1992 (Box 524, Folder 12)
  - Voting record, Associated Builders and Contractors, 2002 (Box 524, Folder 13)
  - Voting record, Bread for the World, 1999-2000 (Box 524, Folder 14)
  - Voting record, Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks, 1990-1994 (Box 524, Folder 15)
  - Voting record, Business-Industry PAC, 1991-1996 (Box 524, Folder 16)
  - Voting record, Campaign for United Nations Reform, 1982-1995 (Box 524, Folder 17)
  - Voting record, Catholics for a Free Choice, 1993 (Box 524, Folder 18)
  - Voting record, Center for National Independence in Politics, 1993 (Box 524, Folder 19)
  - Voting record, Children's Defense Fund Action Council, 1999-2001 (Box 524, Folder 20)
  - Voting record, Christian Coalition, 1992-1998 (Box 524, Folder 21)
  - Voting record, Christian Voice, 1990 (Box 524, Folder 22)
  - Voting record, Citizens for a Sound Economy, 1995 (Box 524, Folder 23)
  - Voting record, Citizens United for Rehabilitation of Errants, 2002 (Box 524, Folder 24)
  - Voting record, Clean Water Action, 1994 (Box 524, Folder 25)
  - Voting record, Committee for Education Funding, 1992-1994 (Box 524, Folder 26)
  - Voting record, Common Cause, 2000 (Box 524, Folder 27)
  - Voting record, Conservative groups, 1990 (Box 524, Folder 28)
  - Voting record, Consumer Federation of America, 1981-1997 (Box 524, Folder 29)
  - Voting record, Council for a Livable World Education Fund, 2002 (Box 524, Folder 30)
  - Voting record, Defenders of Wildlife, 2005-2006 (Box 524, Folder 31)
  - Voting record, Domestic spending, 1981-1986 (Box 524, Folder 32)
  - Voting record, Goldwater Institute, 1992-1995 (Box 524, Folder 33)
  - Voting record, Gun owners, 1992 (Box 524, Folder 34)
  - Voting record, High Frontier, 1992 (Box 524, Folder 35)
  - Voting record, Human Rights Campaign, 1997 (Box 524, Folder 36)
  - Voting record, Humane Society of the United States, 2001 (Box 524, Folder 37)
  - Voting record, Independent Petroleum Association of America, 1990 (Box 524, Folder 38)
  - Voting record, Information Technology Industry Council, 2000 (Box 524, Folder 39)
  - Voting record, International Brotherhood of Boiler Makers, 1992 (Box 524, Folder 40)
  - Voting record, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1989-1996 (Box 524, Folder 41)
  - Voting record, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1992 (Box 524, Folder 42)
  - Voting record, Just Life, 1990 (Box 524, Folder 43)
  - Voting record, Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1981-1992 (Box 524, Folder 44)
  - Voting record, League of Conservation Voters, 1981-1994 (Box 524, Folder 45)
  - Voting record, League of Conservation Voters, 1995-2000 (Box 524, Folder 46)
  - Voting record, League of Property Voters, 1991-1996 (Box 524, Folder 47)
  - Voting record, Liberty Lobby, 1997 (Box 524, Folder 48)
  - Voting record, March for Life, 1991-1992 (Box 524, Folder 49)
  - Voting record, NARAL, 1993-2003 (Box 524, Folder 50)
  - Voting record, NAACP, 1988-1996 (Box 524, Folder 51)
  - Voting record, National Association of Letter Carriers, 1982-1996 (Box 524, Folder 52)
  - Voting record, National Association of Manufacturers, 1982-2000 (Box 525, Folder 1)
  - Voting record, National Association to Protect Individual Rights, 1993 (Box 525, Folder 2)
  - Voting record, National Association of Realtors, 1990-1994 (Box 525, Folder 3)
  - Voting record, National Association of Social Workers, 1990-1998 (Box 525, Folder 4)
  - Voting record, National Breast Cancer Coalition, 2000 (Box 525, Folder 5)
  - Voting record, National Committee for a Human Life Amendment, 1983-1998 (Box 525, Folder 6)
  - Voting record, Republican Conference, 1981-1988 (Box 525, Folder 7)
  - Voting record, Republican Conference, 1981-1995 (Box 525, Folder 8)
  - Voting record, Vetoes, 1992 (Box 525, Folder 9)
  - Voting record, Waste Watch, 2002 (Box 525, Folder 10)
  - Ward leaders meeting, 1982 (Box 525, Folder 11)
  - Fred Waring, 1981 (Box 525, Folder 12)
  - Washington Hotline, Pennsylvania Cable and Telecommunications Association, 1995-1996 (Box 525, Folder 13)
  - Weapons of Mass Destruction Convention, 1999 (Box 525, Folder 14)
  - Welfare reform legislation introduced by Specter, 1981-1994 (Box 525, Folder 15)
  - Western Pennsylvania Businessmen Luncheon, 1984 (Box 525, Folder 16)
  - Pete Wilson, 1994-1995 (Box 525, Folder 17)
  - WQED Pittsburgh, 1995-1996 (Box 525, Folder 18)
- Schedules, 1981-2010; V.
  Schedules contains schedules reflecting the Senator's appointments on any given day. Not as detailed as chronological files, these schedules usually only specify top-level information on the Senator's activities. Material in this series is arranged chronologically.
  - Schedules, 1981 (Box 526, Folder 1)
  - Appointment book, 1981 (Box 526, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, January 1982 (Box 526, Folder 3)
  - Schedules, February 1982 (Box 526, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, March 1982 (Box 526, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, April 1982 (Box 526, Folder 6)
  - Schedules, June 1982 (Box 526, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, July 1982 (Box 526, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, August 1982 (Box 526, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, September 1982 (Box 526, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, October 1982 (Box 526, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, November 1982 (Box 526, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, December 1982 (Box 526, Folder 13)
  - Appointment book, 1982 (Box 526, Folder 14)
  - Schedules, January 1983 (Box 526, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, February 1983 (Box 526, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, March 1983 (Box 526, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, April 1983 (Box 526, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, May 1983 (Box 526, Folder 19)
  - Schedules, June 1983 (Box 526, Folder 20)
  - Schedules, July 1983 (Box 526, Folder 21)
  - Schedules, August 1983 (Box 526, Folder 22-24)
  - Schedules, September 1983 (Box 526, Folder 25)
  - Schedules, October 1983 (Box 526, Folder 26-27)
  - Schedules, November 1983 (Box 527, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, December 1983 (Box 527, Folder 2)
  - Appointment book, 1983 (Box 527, Folder 3)
  - Schedules, January 1984 (Box 527, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, February 1984 (Box 527, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, March 1984 (Box 527, Folder 6)
  - Schedules, April 1984 (Box 527, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, May 1984 (Box 527, Folder 8-10)
  - Schedules, June 1984 (Box 527, Folder 11-12)
  - Schedules, July 1984 (Box 527, Folder 13-14)
  - Schedules, August 1984 (Box 527, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, September 1984 (Box 527, Folder 16-17)
  - Schedules, October 1984 (Box 527, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, October 1984 (Box 528, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, November 1984 (Box 528, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, December 1984 (Box 528, Folder 3)
  - Appointment book, 1984 (Box 528, Folder 4)
  - Appointments, 1984-1992 (Box 528, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, January 1985 (Box 528, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, February 1985 (Box 528, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, March 1985 (Box 528, Folder 9-10)
  - Schedules, April 1985 (Box 528, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, May 1985 (Box 528, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, June 1985 (Box 528, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, July 1985 (Box 528, Folder 14)
  - Schedules, August 1985 (Box 528, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, August 1985 (Box 529, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, September 1985 (Box 529, Folder 2-3)
  - Schedules, October 1985 (Box 529, Folder 4-5)
  - Schedules, November 1985 (Box 529, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, December 1985 (Box 529, Folder 8)
  - Schedules list, 1985-1988 (Box 529, Folder 9)
  - Appointment book, 1985 (Box 529, Folder 10-11)
  - Schedules, January 1986 (Box 529, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, February 1986 (Box 529, Folder 13-15)
  - Schedules, March 1986 (Box 529, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, April 1986 (Box 529, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, April 1986 (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, May 1986 (Box 530, Folder 2-3)
  - Schedules, June 1986 (Box 530, Folder 4-5)
  - Schedules, July 1986 (Box 530, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, August 1986 (Box 530, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, September 1986 (Box 530, Folder 9-10)
  - Schedules, October 1986 (Box 530, Folder 11-12)
  - Schedules, November 1986 (Box 530, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, December 1986 (Box 530, Folder 14)
  - Appointment book, 1986 (Box 530, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, January 1987 (Box 530, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, February 1987 (Box 530, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, March 1987 (Box 530, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, April 1987 (Box 530, Folder 19)
  - Schedules, May 1987 (Box 530, Folder 20)
  - Schedules, June 1987 (Box 530, Folder 21)
  - Schedules, July 1987 (Box 530, Folder 22)
  - Schedules, August 1987 (Box 530, Folder 23)
  - Schedules, September 1987 (Box 530, Folder 24)
  - Schedules, October 1987 (Box 531, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, November 1987 (Box 531, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, December 1987 (Box 531, Folder 3)
  - Appointment book, 1987 (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, January 1988 (Box 531, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, February 1988 (Box 531, Folder 6)
  - Schedules, March 1988 (Box 531, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, April 1988 (Box 531, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, May 1988 (Box 531, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, June 1988 (Box 531, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, July 1988 (Box 531, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, August 1988 (Box 531, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, September 1988 (Box 531, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, October 1988 (Box 531, Folder 14)
  - Schedules, November 1988 (Box 531, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, December 1988 (Box 531, Folder 16-17)
  - Appointment book, 1988 (Box 531, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, January 1989 (Box 531, Folder 19-21)
  - Schedules, February 1989 (Box 531, Folder 22-23)
  - Schedules, March 1989 (Box 532, Folder 1-4)
  - Schedules, April 1989 (Box 532, Folder 5-7)
  - Schedules, May 1989 (Box 532, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, June 1989 (Box 532, Folder 9-10)
  - Schedules, July 1989 (Box 532, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, August 1989 (Box 532, Folder 12-13)
  - Schedules, September 1989 (Box 532, Folder 14-15)
  - Schedules, October 1989 (Box 532, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, November 1989 (Box 532, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, December 1989 (Box 532, Folder 18)
  - Appointment book, 1989 (Box 532, Folder 19)
  - Schedules, January 1990 (Box 532, Folder 20)
  - Schedules, January 1990 (Box 533, Folder 1-2)
  - Schedules, February 1990 (Box 533, Folder 3-6)
  - Schedules, March 1990 (Box 533, Folder 7-11)
  - Schedules, April 1990 (Box 533, Folder 12-15)
  - Schedules, April 1990 (Box 534, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, May 1990 (Box 534, Folder 2-6)
  - Schedules, June 1990 (Box 534, Folder 7-9)
  - Schedules, July 1990 (Box 534, Folder 10-12)
  - Schedules, August 1990 (Box 534, Folder 13-14)
  - Schedules, September 1990 (Box 534, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, September 1990 (Box 535, Folder 1-2)
  - Schedules, October 1990 (Box 535, Folder 3-5)
  - Schedules, November 1990 (Box 535, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, December 990 (Box 535, Folder 8-9)
  - Appointment book, 1990 (Box 535, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, January 1991 (Box 535, Folder 11-14)
  - Schedules, February 1991 (Box 535, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, February 1991 (Box 536, Folder 1-4)
  - Schedules, March 1991 (Box 536, Folder 5-10)
  - Schedules, April 1991 (Box 536, Folder 11-14)
  - Schedules, April 1991 (Box 537, Folder 1-2)
  - Schedules, May 1991 (Box 537, Folder 3-7)
  - Schedules, June 1991 (Box 537, Folder 8-11)
  - Schedules, July 1991 (Box 537, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, July 1991 (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, August 1991 (Box 538, Folder 2-3)
  - Schedules, September 1991 (Box 538, Folder 4-5)
  - Schedules, October 1991 (Box 538, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, November 1991 (Box 538, Folder 8-9)
  - Schedules, December 1991 (Box 538, Folder 10-11)
  - Appointment book, 1991 (Box 538, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, January 1992 (Box 538, Folder 13-15)
  - Schedules, February 1992 (Box 538, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, February 1992 (Box 539, Folder 1-3)
  - Schedules, March 1992 (Box 539, Folder 4-6)
  - Schedules, April 1992 (Box 539, Folder 7-9)
  - Schedules, May 1992 (Box 539, Folder 10-11)
  - Schedules, June 1992 (Box 539, Folder 12-13)
  - Schedules, July 1992 (Box 539, Folder 14-15)
  - Schedules, August 1992 (Box 540, Folder 1-2)
  - Schedules, September 1992 (Box 540, Folder 3-6)
  - Schedules, October 1992 (Box 540, Folder 7-11)
  - Schedules, November 1992 (Box 540, Folder 12-13)
  - Schedules, December 1992 (Box 540, Folder 14-15)
  - Schedules, Invitation log, 1992 (Box 541, Folder 1)
  - Appointment book, 1992 (Box 541, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, January 1993 (Box 541, Folder 3)
  - Schedules, February 1993 (Box 541, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, March 1993 (Box 541, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, April 1993 (Box 541, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, May 1993 (Box 541, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, June 1993 (Box 541, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, July 1993 (Box 541, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, August 1993 (Box 541, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, September 1993 (Box 541, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, October 1993 (Box 541, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, November 1993 (Box 541, Folder 14)
  - Schedules, December 1993 (Box 541, Folder 15)
  - Appointment book, 1993 (Box 541, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, January 1994 (Box 541, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, February 1994 (Box 541, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, March 1994 (Box 541, Folder 19)
  - Schedules, April 1994 (Box 541, Folder 20)
  - Schedules, May 1994 (Box 541, Folder 21)
  - Schedules, June 1994 (Box 541, Folder 22)
  - Schedules, July 1994 (Box 541, Folder 23)
  - Schedules, August 1994 (Box 541, Folder 24)
  - Schedules, September 1994 (Box 541, Folder 25)
  - Schedules, October 1994 (Box 541, Folder 26)
  - Schedules, November 1994 (Box 541, Folder 27)
  - Schedules, December 1994 (Box 541, Folder 28)
  - Appointment book, 1994 (Box 541, Folder 29)
  - Schedules., January 1995 (Box 541, Folder 30)
  - Schedules, February 1995 (Box 542, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, March 1995 (Box 542, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, April 1995 (Box 542, Folder 3)
  - Schedules, May 1995 (Box 542, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, June 1995 (Box 542, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, July 1995 (Box 542, Folder 6)
  - Schedules, August 1995 (Box 542, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, September 1995 (Box 542, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, October 1995 (Box 542, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, November 1995 (Box 542, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, December 1995 (Box 542, Folder 11)
  - Appointment book, 1995 (Box 542, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, January 1996 (Box 542, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, February 1996 (Box 542, Folder 14)
  - Schedules, March 1996 (Box 542, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, April 1996 (Box 542, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, May 1996 (Box 542, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, June 1996 (Box 542, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, July 1996 (Box 542, Folder 19)
  - Schedules, August 1996 (Box 542, Folder 20)
  - Schedules, September 1996 (Box 542, Folder 21)
  - Schedules, October 1996 (Box 542, Folder 22)
  - Schedules, November 1996 (Box 542, Folder 23)
  - Schedules, December 1996 (Box 542, Folder 24)
  - Appointment book, 1996 (Box 542, Folder 25)
  - Schedules, January 1997 (Box 543, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, February 1997 (Box 543, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, March 1997 (Box 543, Folder 3)
  - Schedules, April 1997 (Box 543, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, May 1997 (Box 543, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, June 1997 (Box 543, Folder 6)
  - Schedules, July 1997 (Box 543, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, August 1997 (Box 543, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, September 1997 (Box 543, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, October 1997 (Box 543, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, November 1997 (Box 543, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, December 1997 (Box 543, Folder 12)
  - Appointment book, 1997 (Box 543, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, January 1998 (Box 543, Folder 14)
  - Schedules, February 1998 (Box 543, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, March 1998 (Box 543, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, April 1998 (Box 543, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, May 1998 (Box 543, Folder 18-19)
  - Schedules, June 1998 (Box 544, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, July 1998 (Box 544, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, August 1998 (Box 544, Folder 3)
  - Schedules, September 1998 (Box 544, Folder 4-5)
  - Schedules, October 1998 (Box 544, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, November 1998 (Box 544, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, December 1998 (Box 544, Folder 9-10)
  - Appointment book, 1998 (Box 544, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, January 1999 (Box 544, Folder 12-14)
  - Schedules, February 1999 (Box 544, Folder 15-16)